xbiz.net 2017-07-14

# XBIZ.net - The Adult Industry Social Network

Privacy Policy 

Your privacy is important to Adnet Media (XBIZ™). This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Adnet Media collects on this website, and the ways in which personal information is used. 

Personal information collection

Adnet Media collects information that you provide for the purpose of registering and using this website. 

Using personal information

Adnet Media uses personal information to: 

  * display user profile information accessible to registered users only;
  * notify you about information that may be of interest to you;
  * personalize this website for you;
  * administer this website;
  * enable your access to and use of this website�s services;

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Adnet Media may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights. 

Cookie

Adnet Media uses cookies to store user preferences. 

Disclosure of information

Adnet Media does not disclose personal information to any other organization. 

Secure you data

Adnet Media takes technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website is protected by encryption technology. 

Updating this statement

Adnet Media may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. Please check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes. 

Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children since use of this website by children is strictly prohibited. 

Other websites

This website contains links to other websites. Adnet Media is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party. 

Contact Adnet Media

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us: 

Adnet Media   
5042 Wilshire Blvd, #487   
Los Angeles, CA 90036, USA   
(310) 820-0228
